[{"answer": "What", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ticket.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "They wanna have another meeting? They wanna buy it?! They wanna but it?! Oh! I tell you! We're gonna be rich!! What are we gonna get for this? Fifty, sixty thousand", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "my friend! Now, how are you comparing us to my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ticket.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Yes, you did. You said 'We're my friend'", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "What, is that the one your parents gave you", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ticket.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "All right, we'll be a little late, I,m not taking a cab", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Well, what is it you object to? The comfort? The Speed? The convenience?", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ticket.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Uncle my friend", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "The funny thing i", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ticket.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Oh. Well. You gotta get going, so go", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Oh. Well. You gotta get going, so go", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ticket.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Nobody got a gun to your head", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "what about", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ticket.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I can't, I'm going to the doctor's later", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "No! That's no reason to kill yourself", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ticket.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Every night I sleep in a really hot room, I don't want to kill myself", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Why? It gets hot at night, you can't sleep. You ever tried to sleep in a really hot room", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ticket.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Well, I slept in really hot rooms and I wanted to kill myself", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Yeah, yeah. If I can't be banker, I don't wanna live", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ticket.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "MUST be banker", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "The story is the foundation of all entertainment. You must have a good story otherwise it's just masturbation.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ticket.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Care? Forget about care. Love. They have to love the characters. Otherwise, why would they keep tuning in", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Care? Forget about care. Love. They have to love the characters. Otherwise, why would they keep tuning in", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ticket.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Would they tune in", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Wouldn't tune in", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ticket.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "No tune", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Why him? Why not me", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ticket.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I'm better than him", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "What happened to the muffin", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ticket.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "All of a sudden you get hungry", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I got a little hungry", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ticket.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Yeah! You got a problem with that", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "All of a sudden you get hungry", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ticket.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "No! Enjoy your lunch.  You know a muffin can be very filling.  He's getting a sandwich now", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "You know what I mean", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ticket.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "And why was that", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Would you let me say it? Let me talk", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ticket.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "All right", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Okay", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ticket.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "And that failure to become a banker was eating at you. Eatin", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Yuh, yes. I intend to Your Honor. And then, on the afternoon of September 10th, you received a phone call did you not", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ticket.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Yes, a phone call", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "From you", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ticket.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "You called me", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Yes, from me!! I called you remember", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ticket.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Yes, I called you, you idiot! Because you were going to... You were going to... Remember", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ticket.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "What is your problem", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Hey", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Ticket.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "What are YOU doing here", "qsentId": 50}]